|||||\\\\\\\\\\\\\
Release-Group "Mania" presents
http://doramamania
Mania
Alchemy
Shower
We hire servants in Sosnovy Bor
This is not a letter
What is this then?
If it conveys your feelings, it's a letter
I must have looked pathetic in my attempts.
get here as a servant
You were an incredibly skilled teacher.
I feel sorry for you
Have you at least learned to be faithful?
yes fulfill duties
My teacher tried so hard for me
I thought I should give it my all
Did this stress you out?
Not really. But I doubted
Answer you as a student or as a master
Or answer in the style of what you read
And what did you read?
Then answer the same?
Also? What are you talking about?
It's written right there
"I'll go through anything just to see you"
“I can do anything, just to have the opportunity to see you”
And this is my answer
I missed you too
This is my answer
I'll pretend I didn't hear this
And forget about the letter
Project coordinator and editor: Ria_Lee
You can't get rid of something
Assistant coordinators: Martini, gaarysn
if you've already shared it with someone
You can get rid of
Typesetter translators: Ria_Lee, Tommo, Zero Amamiya
You can burn it
as if it never happened
Do you think you will burn it - and the letter did not exist?
Only here, teacher,
your student
learned to see what cannot be seen
I read Words of the Heart. Do you want to check?
We need to concentrate
to read what you can't see
And then...
say the addressee's name
Moo Deok
A clear but dangerous signal
I'm in love with him
There you go. I read
Something is hard to read because it's hidden,
but it is there
You saw the mark in my eyes, you knew that I was a nomad,
that's how he caught me
Now I saw my other weakness
If this is your weakness,
then mine too
Your letter is my answer
So we have one weakness
I think I don't mind sharing my weakness with you
To be honest, I was worried
You finally got what you wanted
And I couldn't do anything even if you left me
I even thought about poisoning you
and find something to denigrate
Chan Wook,
Apparently you're already poisoned
Poisoned?
You will become weak and infirm
There is no escape from this poison
The antidote is the person who poisoned you
So that's why I missed you
what was poisoned?
Yes
You were mercilessly poisoned by a shadow warrior
Think like this
This is not far from the truth
So it's poison?
Well, yes, it was strange that among everyone
I missed you
You were always threatening to kill me
She even threw a knife at me
Laughed at me, I almost lost my arm
And you have the nerve to lie
You were cruel to me
but I couldn't help but think about you
I open my eyes - I already miss you
I miss you all day, even when I go to bed
- Stop it
- Why?
I confessed my feelings, and you compared them to poison
So at least listen to what my symptoms are.
You are my antidote
I just said that I missed you, you terrible shadow warrior
And you say I'm poisoned
Now bear with my complaints about symptoms
I was poisoned, after all
I have nothing to be ashamed of
Since you are an antidote, that means you are related to the poisoning
This is the nephew of the head of Sosnovy Bor
and our next chapter
I came to greet you on behalf of the head
Congratulations on joining Sosnovy Bor
Well done
You did a good job today
Today you will be offered booze and meat
You can have some fun
Go, eat, drink
Follow me
Mister,
do you know Moo Deok?
She passed the exam today
The servant who came last
One hundred twenty five
Room 125, Moo Deok
Gone!
I know Moo Deok well
She lost consciousness and was taken to Saejukwon
I have to return her things
and give the amulet to enter
Is she still in Saejukwon?
Give it to me. I'll pass it on
You did a good job today
Let's go
Moo Deok...
You're lost because it's in your head
too many thoughts
When this happens, think about one thing
Nak Soo, the only one you think about is Chan Wook
Listen, Yul
I accidentally looked into Moo Deok's bag
and found something strange
This is your whistle, right?
The one you lost in Danhyangok
Yes, my
Then why does Moo Deok have it?
Have you seen Mr. Dan Gu?
He has my things and an amulet for entry
He gave them to me
I see
I'll take
I lost it in Danhyangok. Did you find him there?
Yes
I took it because...
In love with me
You said so yourself
This explanation is enough
I'll pick up my things
and you take the whistle
I told Dan Gu that I gave it to you
I can't take it back
Why are you giving it to me?
You didn't believe it when I confessed my love
Then you had to make me believe
I was just making fun of them
And Moo Deok really loves Yulia
And considering Julia’s gift,
I think he has a soft spot for her too
She probably begged for that whistle
When she needs something
she lies and dodges easily
Yul even knew about her participation in the exam
He answered all the questions for her sake
She definitely asked him to help,
because I'm too stupid myself
She always gets what she wants
What's more important
I saw how cute they were walking together
What?
Cute?
Moo Deok and Yul met once
I think you didn't know because you were locked in the training room.
That's right
Yes, I didn't know
What if this is true?
I missed you too
This is my answer
She refused because she doesn't like me
She didn't miss her like I did
I'm the only one who missed you
I...
I want to drink poison and die
What a shame
I like you
I've told you about this hundreds of times
I don't know much about love
but when you like someone you don't repeat it over and over again
Because it’s hard to admit even once
This whistle
belonged to a friend to whom I could never confess
I really like you
I really wanted to tell her about this
I want to try too
Can I?
You have now entered Sosnovy Bor. We will see each other more often
You can come to me if you need anything
Thank you
Chan Wook read "Words of the Heart"
You helped him, right?
I found out that he could, so I came to tell you
Tell Jin to deliver this book to Jinyeowon.
Bone
Why?
Chang Wook is angry that everyone is reading this “letter”
I think Master Seo Kyung would feel the same way
Apparently you really like Chan Wook
He's special, that's why I watch him
He's very smart
but Jin wants to lock him here
Are you sure
that the ice stone is not in Sosnovy Bor?
Why did you decide this?
20 years ago
Gwangju Chang Gang mastered the alchemy of souls
Because of this
a child was born who should not have
And that night the King's star shone in the sky
Is this Chan Wook?
Yes
The magician unsealed the stone in Sosnovy Bor
and through the alchemy of souls the king's son was born
Jin Moo from Jeonbugwan knows this
If they already have the stone, what excuse can there be?
come up with Pine Forest,
to pick him up?
Jin has no other way to protect Pine Forest than to hide Uka
Why?
Is there something I don't know?
Oh you little one...
How can anyone trust such a careless and imprudent youth with secrets?!
How could you...
I hope it washes off
He's so...
didn't get angry even when I said more
I won't drink chastity tea
Wait, the scarf was a gift from Kim's maid
Cleaning must be completed before
how the magicians will begin their classes. Faster
- Yes
Where is the owner?
- He won't come?
- Well...
I went to wake him up
but he said that he didn’t sleep a wink last night
And he'll take a walk? On the first day?
See you, Moo Deok
Owner
We have to get up
Master!
Wake up
Otherwise I'll hit you
Get up!
Don't make any noise and go, I'll sleep
Are you crazy? Did you want death?
Yes, I'm crazy and I want to die
What's wrong with you?
These are the symptoms of my poisoning
Chan Wook, stop being stubborn and angry
I said I'm the antidote
Here
Here I am
I'm sorry
Hey Chan Wook
I heard you read Words of the Heart. I'm surprised
There is nothing to be surprised
I see you are reading about the Hyonggon technique
I mastered this sword style as a child.
If you teach me to read "Words of the Heart",
I will help you master Hyonggon
We need to think
Agree. Say you agree
Listen, I'm tired of something
Ask Master Li for help
Chan Wook
I mastered Ryusu in about the same time as you
Don't you want to fight me?
Then I'll lend you a sapphire carpet
for training
With its help, energy can be doubled
Sapphire carpet? This is such a rarity
Master, this is a good opportunity.
But such a carpet is cold, right?
I get sick quickly
That's why I don't need this
What are you doing?
I haven't slept well these days, I'm going to take a nap
Missed the chance to master Hyonggon
Are you completely crazy?
And yesterday. The sapphire carpet is hard to come by,
and you said he was cold
I had to agree even if I could die on it
Incredible. "Crazy. Die"
That's all you tell me
Give it here
What are you doing?
You can't lie here together
You will only go to bed if I get up
Get up
And you make
It won't be hard
I said I missed you
and you said I'm poisoned, so I need to sleep and come to my senses
Stop messing with me, at least for a little while.
You just want to upset me
I told you, if I die, you will die too
I'm in agony, you should feel something too
When I sleep I even have cramps
And for how long?
I don't know
What? Upsetting?
Then help me make myself more comfortable
The owner sleeps all the time
Tell him to train
Jeongjingak's magicians train at will
Each person harnesses their energy differently
I won't interfere as long as he doesn't break the rules
But...
Don't worry. Here he is
My head hurts
I'll go home
and I’ll come to my senses, soaking in the water
Does your head hurt? You didn't do anything
And you can't go home either. It's not according to the rules
Yes?
Chan Wook is an exception. He has the head's permission
Why him?
Busy with all sorts of entertainment, you had no time
but I made a deal with the head while I was locked here
I'll be back soon
I'll go with him
If you go, you will be kicked out of here
You tried so hard to get here. Are you ready to just leave?
Chan Wook went home
Are you sure this is correct?
Let him go wherever he wants
Then he will become lazy
Chapter
The lady asks you to wait a little
Is she hosting someone?
I saw Jeonbugwan's servant on the way here
Maybe Deputy Jin Mu is here?
They're not close enough to see each other like that
Just in case, go and check who's leaving
If Master Li wants it that way,
we will hide "Words of the Heart" in Jinyeowon
Did you see anyone else today?
Distant relative
Will Jin Jo Young inherit Jinyoung?
It's not decided yet
My eldest daughter may still be alive
It's been ten years since then
And even though she is blind,
she could sense energy and control relics like no one else
He was a very smart child
Unlike other children,
she was born at 13 months
She was born on the day that Gwangju Chang Gang named
blessed by heaven
Was she born on the day Chang Gang chose for you?
Is it possible
choose the date and time of birth of the child?
It was a coincidence
I would like to invite Master Lee to Jinyeowon
Give him this
Okay
I carried her for 13 months
I can't let her go so easily
I heard the stone has power
bring dead souls back to life
Gwangju
Help me
I came this far to protect my child
I will find you
I'll do my best
to find you
- Did you check who this important guest was?
- Yes
It was Deputy Jin Mu
Since when is the head of Jinyeowon
considers him a member of the family and accepts him?
He quietly left through the back gate
So the meeting was secret
I wonder what tricks he used
slippery Jin Mu to freely visit Jinyoewon?
You're blind so you don't know where you are
You will be silent and do what they ask,
save your life
So that not a sound
Get up
Sit down
Leave her, the rest can go
They are looking for the girl from the portrait
Apparently she's blind
He said the others could go, why no sounds?
You can see
It's a pity. I thought I found the right girl
Kill her
I can do it!
I can be the girl from the portrait
Spare me
You said I'm coming
If you have to be blind,
then I will be like that
Entertaining girl. Get up
So can you pretend to be blind?
I'm already blind
Well, let's check it out
I think I really found what I needed
So be it
From now on, you are Jin Bu Young, Jinyoung's lost daughter.
Yes
I'm Jin Bu Young
Chan Wook stopped training again
How should I punish him this time?
Thanks to me you work hard
Yes
Thanks to you, I'll have to sweep the yard again.
Are you arguing with me?
Then I'll help you leave
You cheated
If I say anything about this, you'll be thrown out of here right away.
Sorry, Your Highness
I'm grateful for the leaves that fell with your help
You can continue shaking the tree
We need to thank
for answers, not for leaves
So you didn’t come to grumble, but for gratitude
It takes me a long time to understand, Your Highness
I am immensely grateful to you
Of course you are grateful. I wrote down the answers myself
Do you even know how to wash ink?
Have you written an answer?
Yes. I'm the Crown Prince
I learned that rice paste removes ink
I even tried it myself, it works
There are simply no words
I am forever in your debt
So what?
Happy to be with your owner?
I heard he read "Words of the Heart"
Yes
Among the magicians of Jeongjingak, he did it the fastest
It's unlikely to be a matter of talent and skills alone
Surely you were lucky again
But he defeated you in a duel
I know what Chan Wook is capable of because I fought him.
Poor sword skills, weak spells
He was lucky to use Tansu. It's not about skills
He's right about something
That's why he came to Jeongjingak. Become a powerful magician
In fact, he lacked the skills to even join Jeongjingak
If he defeats anyone here,
I recognize him
It would be nice to use the Crown Prince
Your Highness
Or maybe we can argue?
Shall we argue?
What do I get from arguing with you?
I'll give you the most precious thing I have
I'll be the first to choose
I'll take red, you take blue
Wait. I'll come there
I missed you too
This is my answer
- Mister
- Yes
I bought your favorite cookies
Are you staying for lunch?
I returned home for a couple of days
- Is this possible?
- The head gave permission
Made me an exception in everything
Of course
You read "Words of the Heart" in a couple of days
It's stupid to force you to follow the same rules as ordinary magicians
Are you happy about my success?
I'm not just happy
You have no idea how proud I am
Maid Kim,
I constantly disappointed you, and now you can be proud
Should I buy you a beautiful dress?
You look
I don't need anything. I feel like I have everything
People came
and told me that you are your father's son
Yes?
Your father was called a genius
And now they say that you are as talented as your father
People said I don't look like him at all
You will make progress
and people won't say anything like that about you anymore
What if there is no success? Will they start spreading rumors again?
No, it's not like that...
Tell them they are free to say whatever they want.
It doesn't bother me anymore
Yes. You can't worry about this anymore
And besides, your successes are your merits
Which side is the father here?
He was never around
And in general, it's all because I
raised you well
You will always be my dear sir,
with or without success
Really?
Then you can go home and be lazy?
Yes, if you want it
But I thought you hated it
If you compare when you returned from Danhyangok,
looked much happier than when they just
chilling at home
That's why I couldn't stop you, despite all the danger
I want
so that you succeed in everything you choose for yourself
Yes
I have to go back
Are you leaving?
Yes. If you asked me to leave, I would do the opposite
But after such a speech, we must return
I have to do my best to make you proud
And the head? Doesn't it hurt anymore?
No
Both people and horses
teach with carrot and stick
They just whipped me
Who dared to hit you?
Don't worry, I won't just stand there while they beat me.
Wrap me some sweets
A bunch of cookies
- It will be fun
- Are you sure?
Chan Wook
You're finally here
Yes
It feels like you've all been waiting for me
Does everyone want the cookies I brought?
Go to the study hall. It will be fun
- Were you waiting for me?
- Yes
I'll be your first opponent
What?
Let's start the fight
If you refuse, you lose.
What are you talking about?
Take
Chan Wook lost
Gyo Ho, the winner, can take back his golden toad
What's going on?
I bet
I didn't argue with you about anything, Your Highness.
Not with you, with your maid
I told her that you can't defeat a single magician here.
you can't
And your maid said that you will win at least one
Moo Deok said that?
You will fight every day for ten days
If you never win,
she will give me the most precious thing she has
Expensive?
What's your favorite thing?
What you gave me
It's on the line
This jade looks expensive, I want it for myself
That's why I brought golden toads
as a prize
If you don't win before the toads are over,
this will be mine
I have little interest in such a debate
I wasn't arguing with you, but with her
If you give up
that means she didn’t win a single fight, that means she lost
And this will be mine
Owner
This is the most valuable thing I have ever received.
Please take him back
Look only
You really got the golden toad
Let Uk read "Words of the Heart"
- but he doesn’t wield a sword well
- What's going on?
The prince and Moo Deok had an argument
The Crown Prince brought golden toads, so everyone wants to participate
Strong magicians line up
Put it down
His Highness laughed at you
As your teacher, I could not remain silent
Don't lie. I know you
I've been lazy these couple of days
that's why you made a bet for me to train
Yes
You'll have to fight dozens of magicians whether you like it or not.
The first fight was even more disappointing
The step is heavy, you move the sword slowly
- Tomorrow is a duel with...
- I refuse
Even if you lose, you will remember what you saw,
this will help you
- I won't fight
- Ten fights -
ten different styles
- Moo Deok...
- Master,
you can safely go home and soak
Then you'll never get that jade back
Okay, okay
You argued
But...
Why did you put my gift?
You know it yourself
This was the only way to make you fight and win
When I said I missed you
Is this what you meant by my weakness?
Yes
You probably hate me now
but you can't lose what belongs to us both
Is that why you said I was poisoned?
If you return it, I will smile wide at you
Instead of an antidote
Chan Wook
Bring him back any way
This is the most valuable thing I've ever had
received in my entire life
Is he really dear to you?
Or...
Is it just very expensive?
I'll take it from the Crown Prince
It's strange to have something paired with him
But it wasn’t worth sharing with you either
I heard you visit Saejukwon often
Maybe you want to appoint Master Huo as your teacher
and learn magic from him?
What are you talking about?
You are my teacher
I only go there for treatment
I breathe fresh air. Plus, funny things often happen there
You must enjoy spending time with the magicians of Sosnovy Bor
I communicate with Yul, my cousin
Park Dan Gu is also fun
Ah Chan Wook... I'd like to teach him a lesson, but it's not that easy
He seems thrilled to have read Words of the Heart.
so today I put it in its place
He lost to a magician who had just mastered Ryusu
Now people know its true power
Nobody admires him anymore
Beautiful jade
I exchanged it for ten golden toads
- Is he that valuable?
- It has Yin energy
Where's the other half?
Second half?
Objects with opposite energy always have a pair
There must also be red jade
They only have value as a pair
So he has a date?
Eunuch O
If people have twins, what could that mean?
This means they are married or dating
Damn it
Don't you like this jade, Your Highness?
Yes, he pisses me off. Gets on my nerves
Take it and break it into little pieces
You can't do this
Chan Wook can win it back
If he returns it,
then they will become a couple again
That's it
- Master Li
- Yes...
What brought you here?
I've been wearing hemp clothes all year and never felt cold
But
I should have worn this scarf
I realized how cold I was
What's that there?
What...
Never in my life have flowers seemed beautiful to me,
but once I saw these, I wanted to give them to you
Beauty
Is this for me?
These books...
You have good books here
Great book
Maid Kim...
Are you sick?
She hasn’t appeared in Sosnovy Bor for a long time
She went there yesterday
She often visits Mr. Chan
Here's how
She just didn't come see me
She has a guest now
Guest? Who?
I don't know him, but he's a young man
Young man?
As far as I know, Maid Kim doesn't know any young men.
Maid Kim
Hello
What kind of weeds are these?
These are flowers
- What other weeds?
- Maid Kim
Were you offended because I was rude that day?
Is that why they stopped coming?
I really didn't know. Thought you were sick
I was worried and came here
You shouldn't have come
You said you'd never come here
When did I say that?
You're wrong
But still
I'm glad you're healthy
If they were so worried about my health,
could at least bring weeds
Do you need weeds?
I'll bring them
I don't need them
I'm not asking you for weeds, but for flowers.
I want you to show
your concern,
giving me something beautiful
My guest is still here, you better leave
Maid Kim
Well...
When you come to visit Uka,
I hope you'll come see me
Wait...
Drives me because
that I came empty-handed?
Maid Kim
How cold-blooded
Since his shoes are smaller than mine,
that means he's shorter
Do you like sweets?
Yes
Delicious
Then take some more
This is for me
- How do I look?
- Very beautiful
- Try it on
- Me?
So how?
They hang him here
Look, flowers
You said that you should buy flowers
I need them to decorate Boo Young unnie's room
This time, apparently, they found her
Really? Did Jin Mu find her?
It's still a secret
I hope unnie comes back
Then you won't become Jinyaewon
But I can marry whoever I want
It will be possible to marry the one you love
Glad to hear
Then we need to break off our fake engagement
Thanks for pretending to be my fiancé
I didn't pretend
My feelings
sincere
You will become the head soon
Would you marry me? Would you join our family and leave everything?
Yeah
I guess I worried for nothing
I was even preparing for
that I will be kicked out of the family
Are you serious?
Did you want to give up your status as head of Sosnovy Bor for my sake?
You said you don't want a loveless marriage
Then I thought, if we get married,
you will have a loving husband
Therefore...
Well, you have yet to meet the one you love
It seems I'm already
I met him
If you hold on to me like this,
I'll never let go
My feelings are too strong
There's no turning back
You need to buy flowers to propose properly.
Let's go
Send these flowers to the Chan family
Did someone die?
Why are you sending them chrysanthemums?
I almost made a big mistake
Exactly
From here
all the way to here
Send everything
- All these flowers?
- Yes, that's it
- I'm sure she'll like at least something.
- It can't be
Thank you very much
-Which ones do you like?
- These are these
I can buy everything if you want
You are the future head of Sosnovy Bor
Why are you meeting with the future head of Jinyowon?
Why?
Do you want to give up your inheritance and join their family?
Uncle, we love each other
Not long ago Cho Young
loved Uka
No. Today she proved it to me
Jo Young Says She Will Give Up Her Head Title For Love
They only have one daughter
Who will become the head of Jinyeowon then?
She will be the eldest daughter
Jeonbugwan's magicians help them find her missing sister
What?
Deputy Jin Mu comes to see them every day
Jin Mu?
If only I had a brother
who will become the head instead of me
I'm asking purely out of curiosity
Uncle, are you sure you don’t have a child on your side?
None?
At all?
Get out
What?
Away!
It's not too late, you can have a child now
You...
I mean, you're still full of strength
Catch this scoundrel!
Well, well
Why are there so many flowers here?
I had a fight with one person. So he's trying to make peace
I hope you forgive him. These flowers are beautiful
you are so kind
Young Master Chan's mother...
was as kind as you
Apparently, Uk went into it
Mister?
What made you think that?
When he talked about his mother,
I felt warmth
I saw it in his eyes
Wait a minute...
Did he talk to you about his mother?
You must be very close to him
Not at all
Only Young Master Chan wants to get closer
Last time he spent 4 hours with his mistress
Is it true?
We just talked for a bit
It turns out it's you. Egret
The gentleman may be cold, he has suffered in the past
And how to open up to someone - kind and caring
Come visit us more often
Consider this place your nest
and come here often
Okay
Jin Moo helps Jin Ho Kyung find his daughter?
I think this is just an excuse
visit Jinyeowon
I think Jin Moo wants to get Jinyeowon's support
If he succeeds,
he will be able to resist Sosnovy Bor
And then...
he and his people without fear and regrets
will reveal to the world the power of the ice stone
One of Jin Mu's people has the stone
Everyone thinks the stone is made of ice,
but the forces of fire, water and wind are concentrated in it
200 years ago, a magician from the Choi family created a reflector
And now someone is using the power of the stone to do it again.
New batch of reflectors made by the Queen
Evil does not lie in the power of the ice stone.
The reflector is what is used for evil purposes
A power that is beyond the control of an ordinary person,
will want to have everything if it becomes available
The power to leave the old body
and take a new one
Old body in exchange for young, ugly for beautiful
The power to stop death and make life eternal
He is a young, healthy and wonderful young man
He was chosen...
my successor
I want to migrate into his body
Master
What spell did you want to show me?
Alchemy of souls
Alchemy of souls?
I still have so many things to do
but this body is no good, the disease brings his imminent death closer
Therefore...
I need your body
What?
Let's start with the alchemy of souls
Master, I don't want to switch bodies
If I switch bodies with you, I will soon die
But your body will live
Help
Save me
Help me! Help!
Master!
Master
My body...
Take it all back
Please. I don't want to die
Master! Give me my body
Master! I want to return to my body
Master!
Alchemy of souls helped save the life of another
valuable magician
While we
we wield the power of stone,
our souls will be able to live forever, and not rot in these bodies
Now the power of the stone is prohibited,
so you have to do alchemy secretly
But sooner or later the day will come when our strength will grow stronger
We will show everyone that we are right. Our hard work will pay off
And on this day
everyone here...
will conquer death and gain eternal life
Have you seen everything?
Yes
You must bring one person here
Jin Ho Kyung will become your mother. Get closer to her
And then bring her here
Can you handle it?
Yes
She comes up
If you can bring Jin Ho Kyung here,
it will be easier to reveal the power of the stone to the whole world
Why aren't you sleeping yet?
Jin Mu can become
stronger and more influential than we think
Surely the King's star appeared to eliminate the chaos caused by the stone
Are you talking about Uke?
Master So Kyung, who prevented the horror of two hundred years ago,
was also born under a similar star
This star was created by magic
She can't be compared to the star of Master Seo Kyung
Did I mention that the star is the same?
So I'm curious
I wonder if this star will slowly go out
or will it shine brightly?
Victory!
- Excellent
- Good job
I knew it
I knew about Tansa
The prince didn't know, so you did it
And even water from the puddle that everyone saw
As easy as shelling pears
Victory!
- Great!
- Marvelous!
Only three toads left?
Yes
So he's been fighting for the last seven days straight?
And I kept losing
I thought he would stop if he kept losing
Apparently he's trying for this
As you said, he doesn’t wield a sword well, his spells are weak
But he continues to fight...
just because he's annoying
These are just fights, but he fights with other magicians every day
He's definitely exhausted
Your Highness, I believe in your victory
Even I didn't have a chance to fight the magicians of Jeongjingak
But I let Chan Wook do it...
for your own golden frogs
Has Won Moo Deok fooled me again?
Fight and lose, Chan Wook
Everything that doesn't kill you
only makes you stronger
Thanks for watching with us!
http://doramamania
Alchemy
Shower
- Chan Wook!
-Have you come to the owner?
Let him lose, he gets stronger
Don't go
Don't go to your room, stay here
What a horror! Look at the shoes. All wet
You're hurt
There is commotion in the capital. Last night he was attacked by several assassins
- Don't kill him!
- Kill him!
- He's a nomad
- Come out!
- I'm coming in
- Chan Wook
I don't think it's right to let go of a magician who just got here so easily
Once you go wild, you can't go back
You can't become a man, only a monster
We can protect the monsters of this world